here I am Zelensky you are Putin what should we
вот я Зеленский вы Путин что мы должны
do to stop the war you
сделать чтобы остановить войну вы бы мне
could tell me okay look Vova there
могли сказать ладно вот смотри Вов там
yes Okay I give you these lands that
да Хорошо я тебе отдаю эти земли которые
you as if you think so You said
ты как бы ты считаешь так Вы же сказали
that he did not want to seize
что он не хотел захватить
the lands good afternoon Hello I am from
земли добрый день Здравствуйте я из
Ukraine city Khmelnitsky Where are you from
Украины город Хмельницкий Вы откуда
Russia Ufa Ufa you are a Bashkort Yes I understand you
Россия Уфа Уфа вы башкорт Да понял
will support the special operation and
спецоперацию поддержите да
if you support it they haven't called you up
на фронте если поддержите не призвали
yet Ponya And you are some kind of
пока Поня А вы какой-то
military man they are already calling you up and can you
военный там даже уже призывают а можете
tell me When I meet people
мне сказать Вот я когда встречаю людей
who support the special operation How did
которые поддерживают спецоперацию А как
it happen that  a year ago Putin
так получилось что год назад Путин
announced a special operation to protect Donetsk
объявлял спецоперацию о защите Донецкой
and Lugansk regions yes And now he can't
и Луганской области да А теперь не может
protect Bryansk Belgorod
защитить брянскую Белгородскую
Why are you asking me So you live
Почему меня спрашиваете Так вы пожи
Russia I thought a year ago That this is
Росси я вот думал год назад Что это
really a special operation to
действительно спецоперация чтобы
protect Donetsk Lugansk people now
защитить донецких луганских людей теперь
I see in Donetsk Lugansk region
смотрю в Донецкой Луганской области
they bombed cities there Mariupol  Maryinka
разбомбили города там Мариуполь марьинка
Severodonetsk yes that is clearly they were not
Северодонецк да то есть явно их не
protected but only killed a bunch of people
защитили а только поубивали куча людей
deprived of shelter And now you also have all sorts of margarines in the Bryansk region What is your name Andrey Andre cut please I of course to be honest I can't quite wrap my head around this But here is your opinion because of what let's say Well okay Putin in general well, in particular, let's say, all this was started and all this began Well, look The thing is that the grandfather has been in power for too long and has come to believe that he is almost the Emperor of All Russia and so he is fueled by your society, which is infected with imperial ideas that it is necessary to restore the Soviet Union Andrey well well not you you asked my opinion I am telling you Yes Pony Well this is somehow completely well why not look at me me in me in chat roulette every second Russian says that Kyiv is a Russian city Odessa is a Russian city and so on Andrey So what? Well, according to you, then let's have your version. No, I, I, that's exactly what I don't know. Well,  Well, here's yours,
не знаю то Ну а вот Ну вот ваша вот
look, based on the level of development, you
смотрите вот по уровню развития вы всё
can still put forward some version
равно можете какую-то версию выдвинуть
of your own. Here's your version, but it seems to me that we don't know it and I definitely don't know it because Well, what if it's just the version that we'll be thinking about?  this is the
версия про которую мы будем думать это
version Let's just try
та версия Давайте просто попробуем
different weights It seems to me that it is so
разный вес Мне кажется она настолько
deep that it Well, not really E I'm just an
глубока что это Ну не совсем Э я просто
ordinary civilian that is, yes,
обычный Гражданский человек то есть да
who is not not just not just You
который не не просто не просто Вы же
said that you support That is, it
сказали что вы поддерживаете То есть вы
turns out that you don't know why
получается не знаете из-за чего
the special operation  but you support well roughly
спецоперация но поддерживаете ну грубо
speaking How in the sense of your own it is clear that well
говоря Как в смысле сво понятно что ну
here you communicate when there in chat
здесь общаешься когда же там в чат
roulette Well, all the same, they are also ordinary people
рулетки Ну все же тоже обычные люди
who roughly speaking go to the factory yes and
которые грубо говоря ходят на завод да а
here he is in chat roulette he turns out to be
здесь он в чат рулетке он оказывается
such a politician He knows everything yes Well look
такой политик Он всё знает да Ну смотри
Yes  but he is in his own country, that is, wait
Да но он в своей стране то есть подожди
Your troops came to Ukraine to kill
Твои войска пришли в Украину убивать
people You support this but you don't know
людей ты это поддерживаешь но не знаешь
why Well here again I don't know
из-за чего Ну здесь опять-таки я не знаю
of course what to compare with what is correct to
конечно с чем сравнить с чем правильно
compare with yes such a situation
сравнить да такую ситуацию
but there are moments, roughly speaking
но бывают же грубо говоря моменты
some when Well, it seems like the person has
какие-то когда Ну вроде бы человек на
n't yet  attacked but you have to
тебя ещё не напал но тебе приходится
hit first, so to speak,
бить первым условно говоря
wait one more time Do you know why your
подожди ещ раз Вы знаете из-за чего ваша
country attacked my country I don't
страна напала на мою страну я не
know You know, there seem to be reasons You don't know
знаю Знаете каже есть причи Вы не знаете
why but you support this attack It
почему но вы поддерживаете это нападение
seems to me that there is a reason that
Мне кажется есть причина что не просто
all this is not just like that  and what, well, just like that,
так всё это затесь и что ну просто так
just take and start such a special
просто так взять и начинать такую спец
military operation Well, I understand there are
военную операцию Ну поня извет
versions, but I don’t really remember them
версии есть но особо я там не помню
Now, to be honest Well, how did he attack
Сейчас если честно Ну ну как он напал
just like that or was there something for something,
просто так или за что-то там было
damn, well, a little bit It seems to me
что-то блин ну немножко Мне кажется
mentality so to speak I don't know how or
менталитет так скажем я не знаю как или
were there some concepts 70 years ago
понятия какие-то были 70 лет назад
a little It seems to me different What kind of
немножко Мне кажется иные Какие какие у
mentality did Hitler have Well I mean I
Гитлера были менталитет Ну я имею в виду
don't know Well they treated life differently
не знаю Ну по-другому к жизни относились
then It seems to me anyway in general Well
тогда мне кажется всё равно в целом Ну
how not  I know, well, he attacked Look, Hitler
как не знаю нуну напал Смотри вот Гитлер
attacked Yes, the Soviet Union Yeah, and
напал Да на Советский Союз Ага и
Well, well, in fact, it turns out he got screwed and here is the
Ну ну по факту получается огрёб во и тут
situation too, it is not clear what attacked,
такая ситуация тоже непонятно что напал
right there Putin, it is not clear what attacked and it
тут же Путин непонятно что напал и
turns out, in fact, he
получается по факту
cut off the second
отре секун
contract
договор
Well, that's it  no
Ну это нет
but you are talking about the
но вот вы говорите допустим про
Soviet Union, for example, something in a year if you
Советский Союз Ну что-то за год если
take 72 years if in a year
взять 72 года если за год
from the Soviet Union Well, I don't know, is there
от Советского Союза Ну я не знаю там
some percentage there No, it
процент есть какой-нибудь Нет это что-то
seems to me that it's very slow for you Then I
мне кажется вам совсем медленно Тогда
didn't understand anything at all  I don't understand Well, you
ничего не понял вообще не понял Ну вы
say that Putin
говорите что Путин
wants yes, but it doesn't seem like it's happening very slowly
хочет да но что-то совсем медленно не
and what will be the consequences of this yes, so
кажется и что последствии этого да так
look, you know, this is when, for example, a
смотри это знаешь это когда например
drunk thug decides to grab a phone from
гопник бухой так решил отжать телефон у
some guy, but it turns out that here,
какого-то малого так а оказалось тут
in short, he's not really a guy, so  And the kid
короче он не совсем малой так А малой
went to kickboxing And Lupa starts and
ходил на кикбоксинг Да и начинает Лупа и
this thug takes out a knife
гопник такой оп достаёт ножик
and there are some guys standing behind the kid saying, not a
а за малым ещё ребята стоят говорят не
kid, look, you have a gun so you can
малой смотри на тебе пистолет чтобы ты
protect yourself
защитился
and set a good example I agree and
и пример хороши Я согласен и гопник
this thug yells If you didn't have
такой орёт Если бы у тебя не было
a gun I would have you  took I would have
пистолета Я бы тебя забрал Я бы тебе
beaten you up like that and then you stuck your nose in thinking
навалял так и тут вы сунулись думали
Now a couple of weeks in short and that's it, everyone here
Сейчас пару недель короче и всё все тут
will hang up their bast shoes and surrender so they got
лапти повесят и сдадутся так получили
a beating and the whole world saw that you have an
звездюлей и весь мир увидел что у вас не
insolvent army, an insolvent
состоятельная армия не состоятельно
state Well, that's all A  now they just well
государство Ну и всё А теперь просто ну
and they don't know how to
и уже не знают как это
go out with a good face it would be
с хорошим лицом выйти бы уже не
impossible to go out with a good face so they're trying to go out, trying to
получится с хорошим лицом выйти вот и
go out, well, no, well, I kind of
долбятся долбятся ну Ну нет ну я как бы
again, to be honest, I also don't know what the
опять если честно тоже не знаю какая там
situation is there but it looks like it looks like that it
ситуация но Похоже Похоже на то на то
looks like that  I wouldn't say that I mean
похоже как бы я я не говорю что в смысле
I'll be there now there defending what
я там буду сейчас там отстаивать то что
Yes no Yes what if we want there
Да не Да вы что если мы захотим там
now no well well you would I would laugh I would
сейчас нет ну ну ты бы я бы ржал я бы
already laugh Yes it was still possible to believe it a year ago
уже ржал Да это ещё год назад ещё можно
Well about the Soviet  The Union
было поверить Ну про Советский Союз
is real but it seems to me that it is a little
реально но мне кажется это немножко
something of some kind Here
что-то какой-то Вот
is Lenin who created Ukraine that this is the Armed Forces
ре это Ленин создал Украину что это ВС
Russians are angry and did not voice it It was not I who
русские зли н озвучивал Это не я
came up with it now the EU World Cup Zelensky speak
придумал сечас ЕС ЧМ Зеленский говори
Zele let's what Zele
зеле давайте что зеле гово с вообще
talk about in general I say I don't say now Specifically what I
говорю не говорю сечас Конкретно что я
specifically  I can say that yes Putin
конкретно могу сказать что да Путин
said yes about the fact that these are their
говорил да о том что это их земли
historical lands Well no that the lands
исторические Ну нет что зем
somewhere I think I even saw a recording of Zelensky
гдето помоему даже видел запись зеленски
saying that if he becomes president he
говорит что он если будет президентом он
will stop the war So he is stopping it
прекратит войну Так он и прекращает
now
сейчас
Yes but you think that like  now
Да но вы считаете что вот как бы сечас
Zelensky is doing everything right what is
Зеленский всё правильно делает что
wrong He is defending his country what is
неправильно Он защищает свою страну что
he doing wrong Well damn well I
он неправильно делает Ну блин ну я на
actually saw one guy in Cha
самом деле в Ча одного парня видел
who is young lalo
который коне молодой лало
no We are also allowed As
нет У нас тоже разрешается Как
if again it seems to me that we are a little to
бы опять-таки мне кажется мы немного
be honest both Lukam Poche  Well, I don't know
если честно оба Лукам Поче Ну не знаю
because the way our special services
потому что как у нас здесь спецслужб
work here is the same as yours. And what do we have?
работают также и у вас А что у нас
Look, we have Here was Don't say what
смотри у нас Вот был не говори что у
you have, let's see. Look,
вас давай вот посмотрим смотри был у
Poroshenko
Порошенко
won, so the special services were under him, so that's
выиграл так под ним были спецслужбы так
all. And what did he come for?
всё что И что он пришёл были выборы
Zelensky won the elections, the services did nothing, they did
выиграл Зеленский ниче службы не делали
n't remove the candidate there. Well, and now,
там не убирали кандидата Ну так а сейчас
what kind of purges are you having, what purges? I
Какие зачистки у вас какие зачистки Да
don't know, well, no matter how you look at the teleg
не знаю ну там как не посмотришь в teleg
channels, Zelensky is doing all sorts of things, what is he
каналах там Зеленский там что только не
doing, what is he doing, no,
творит что что творит что он творит нет
I'm interested, no, that's it  what do you have there I
ям интересно нет так что там у васна
remember the names What kind of purges
запоминаю фамили Какие зачистки что он
did he do there they come and cut out those who are against they
делал там приходят вырезают те кто проти
don't get out I see I mean Well some well
не вылезают Понятно В смысле Ну какие-то
in the media space Yes they remove In
ну в медийном пространстве Да убирают В
I mean, some candidates there Who Well
смысле там каких-то кандидатов Кого Ну
who
кого
was removed Well, I'm telling you Andrey I'm you Well,
убрали Ну я же говорю Андрей я же те Ну
look I I for example say you
вот смотри я я я например говорю у вас
took Navalny imprisoned Well Navalny is
Навального взяли посадили Ну Навальный
here too, so I at
же тоже здесь вот я сколько по крайней
least not Well, I'm telling you an example of
мере не Ну вот я вам пример говорю
Navalny  they took Nemtsov, they killed him,
Навального взяли посадили Немцова убили
yes, all of them, those who
Да всех Вот таких которые кандидатами
would have been candidates for president, what do we have, the
были б на президента что у нас то же
same thing, what do you have, what do we have, Well, I told you, who of the
самое подобное у вас про что у нас Ну я
presidential candidates was imprisoned, who was killed, Well, look, here it is
президенты убили кого Ну смотри ты здесь
clear that you can be more like that  let
понятно что ты может быть более так
's say again savvy Well if you are not
скажем опять подкован Ну если вы не
savvy then why voice it This is the
подкован то зачем такое озвучивать Это
voice I am telling you I am just the one
голос Я же тебе говорю я просто который
in Telegram channels I am telling you that A I
в Telegram каналах Тебе же говорю что А
understood By the way I by the way saw a video in a Telegram
понял Я кстати я кстати видел в Telegram
channel of some Chechen you
канале видео как какой-то чеченец вас
there well I don't remember  exactly in short here in
там ну я не помню точно короче вот в
which Telegram channel Well I saw Here
каком Telegram канале Ну видел Вот
really you were and Ramzan Kadyrov has
реально вы были да и у Рамзана Кадырова
some assistant there he insult
там какой-то помощник он оскорбление
go No it's not like that Why look I'm
перейти Да не так Почему смотри я вам
showing you without I in Russian stupidly like
показываю без я по-русски безглуздо типа
eh Well, the laughter of this situation is the message that
ээ Ну смех вот этой ситуации посыла что
I am referring to the Telegram channel that I
я ссылаются на Telegram канале что я
saw something I don’t know that you can
что-то видел не знаю что так можно что
say anything like that No, no If you
угодно говорить Нет ну нет Если ты
say something like that I mean to you if
скажешь такого я же тебе имею виду если
you say something like that, then I’ll
ты такое скажешь такого не то я тебе
tell you Well  probably well you see yes that
скажу Ну наверное ну вот видите да то
is if we speak then we should speak with
есть мы должны если говорить то говорить
some real things not like that Because you
какими-то реальными вещами не так Потому
can say anything like that Well no well
что так можно что угодно говорить Ну нет
I agree I mean But I'm
ну я согласен В смысле Но я же тебе
just telling you that as I know that
просто говорю что как я знаю что
purges are taking place I mean I'm burning
проходят зачистки в смысле горю
nusi of course the example is very bad Well
нуси конечно пример очень плохо Ну а
why Well I don't know You can't an example of
почему Ну не знаю Вы не можете пример
purges And I can't an example of a
зачисток А я не могу пример
Chechen Well you see And I
чеченце ну вот видите А мне мне
don't like what you think examples about
неприятно что вы вы думаете примеры про
purges Well you think that Zelensky is
зачистки Ну ты считаешь что Зеленский
doing everything right and he is a good
всё правильно делат и он хороший
president Yes A  do you think that Kadyrov
президент Да А вы считаете что Кадыров
didn't do this? None of the Kadyrovites are here,
вот не делал Никто из кадыровцев
well, you see,
вас нет ну всё видите я считаю
I think I could have
мне каже мог бы всё-таки
done it anyway, so that Well, at least
сделать так чтобы Ну по крайней мере
understand that let's do it, here I am Zelensky,
понять что так давайте вот я Зеленский
you are Putin, what should we do to
вы Путин что мы должны сделать чтобы
stop the war,
остановить войну
but it seems to me  again me today
но мне кажется опять-таки я сегодня по
regarding this I thought that he was saying
поводу этого думал что он говорит
let's say and you could tell me okay
допустим и вы бы мне могли сказать ладно
look Vova there yes Okay I'm
вот смотри Вов там да Хорошо я тебе
giving you these lands that you kind of
отдаю эти земли которые ты как бы ты
think so You said that he didn't
считаешь так Вы же сказали что он не
want to seize the land no Yes I say Well I
хотел захватить земли нет Да говорю Ну в
mean Well I understand  right now I mean there
смысле Ну понятно же сейчас же В смысле
is a question of lands Well, as if but
идёт же вопрос земель Ну как бы но
Wait
Подожди
Look anyway How is it going supposedly
Смотри всё же Как идёт якобы
And there was a referendum What referendum Well,
А был референдум Да какой референдум Ну
as if some referendum you entered with
как бы референдум какой вы вошли
troops made some kind of referee there
войсками сделали там какой-то рефере
go I Zelensky you Putin your
идите я Зеленский вы Путин ваше
proposal to give to you Well  offer
предложение отдать вам Ну предложение
briefly say Give us such and
коротко скажи Отдайте намм такие-то
such lands come on Yes, let's
такие-то земли давай Да вот я тебе
say you give us these lands everything
допустим ты отдаёшь нам эти земли всё
let's say yes I understand that everything I like
допустим да понима что всё я я как
Zelensky Yes I listened to your offer
Зеленский Да послушал ваше предложение
I say look Vladimir Vladimirovich I
говорю смотрите Владимир Владимирович я
listened carefully to your offer I
внимательно выслушал ваше предложение я
say which with  it's just that at
говорю которые с просто это а момент
what moment and you, for example, start saying that it's
какой и ты например начинаешь говоришь
good that the lands were given away but to put pressure on Russia,
хорошо земли отдали но давить на Россию
well, with the same sanctions and all the
ну теми же самыми санкциями и всеми
economic ways I understand, super Yes, I
путями экономически Поня супер Да понял
understand, I understand your proposal Give these
понял ваше предложение Дави этими
lands to Vladimir Vladimirovich Yes
землями Владимир Владимирович Да
look I consulted with I The fact is
смотрите я посоветовался с я Дело в том
that I am not the Tsar of Ukraine As you are the Tsar of Russia
что я не царь Украины Как вы царь России
Yes Yes I am the elected president I must
да Да я избранный президент я должен
express the will of the people so I bring to
выражать волю народа так вот доношу к
you the will of the Ukrainian people You must
вам волю украинского народа Вы должны
follow the course of the Russian
последовать за курсом российского
ship We will not give you a drop of our
корабля мы Не отдадим Вам ни капли нашей
Land  so on the contrary with the help of the entire
Земли так а наоборот с помощью всего
civilized world and Western weapons
цивилизованного мира и западного оружия
Yes we will give
Да мы дадим
you Uh-huh You uh get out of the borders of Ukraine in
вам Угу Вы ээ свалить за границы Украины
the state of ninety-one Crimea
состоянием на девяносто первый год Крым
Donetsk Lugansk will return to Ukraine
Донецк Луганск вернётся в состав Украи
So and we, as part of the international
Так а мы ещё в составе международной
coalition, will be engaged in
коалиции так будем заниматься
the decolonization of Russia you disintegration into
деколонизации России вы распад на
independent states including yours
независимые государства в том числе ваш
here you have people living in Bashkortostan
вот у вас есть там люди в Башкортостане
Let them be Independent Bashkartastan
живут Да будут Независимый башкартастан
Tatarstan Sakha Yakutia in the Caucasus the peoples
Татарстан Саха Якутия на Кавказе народы
will gain independence so there will be
обретут независимость так будут
regional states Ural
региональные государство Уральская
People's Republic Far Eastern
народная республика Дальневосточная
People's Republic so you most likely
народная республика так вас скорее всего
as a result of the patriotic Maidan
в результате Майдана патриотического
After the defeat in Ukraine they will demolish  so that
После поражения в Украине снесут так то
means you will have a lot of dissatisfied
есть у вас будет очень много недовольных
people there  the riflemen
там всякие стрелковые пригожиным на вас
will hang all the dogs on you, Prigozhin, so they
повесят всех собак так вас где-то там
will throw you out of a window somewhere from the Kremlin or
скинут из окна с Кремля или вы там
strangle you with a scarf or a snuffbox and hit you
задушит шарфом или табакерка и ударят
like that, we will still be there, after I
так мы будем я ещё после того как
stop being president, I will return to
перестану быть президентом вернусь в
humor, eh,
юмор э В девяносто пятом квартале
I will put up another post about this in the ninety-fifth quarter  such a scene so uh
поставлю про это ещё такую сценку так э
Putin falls out of the Kremlin window so I
Путин выпадает из окна Кремля так вот я
will give birth to you until the end of my days and
буду рожать с вас до конца своих дней а
you will be inglorious
вы будете бесславный
I see How do you like our negotiating
Понятно Как Вам наша переговорная
position
позиция
agree let it be so well okay
согласны пусть пусть будет так ну ладно
let it be so good look let's make an
пусть будет так хорошо смотрите давайте
undercut let it be so this is the best
подрез мы Пусть будет так это наилучшие
negotiations between Zelensky and
переговоры Зеленского и
Putin
Путина
Well, your opinion in the end Why did Russia
Ну Ваше мнение в итоге Почему Россия
attack Ukraine, they
напала на Украину на
said, in order to seize
теми сказали для того чтобы захватить
territories
территории
there, something, that's why the
там чего-нибудь вот в результате захваты
hell is it needed Andrey, just
А нафига она нужна Андрей вот просто
tell me what I'm saying because the
скажи мне то что я же говорю потому что
old man decided, yes, what  he is restoring the
дед решил да что он восстанавливает
Soviet Union he is the emperor of the Russian
Советский Союз он император Российской
Empire And so on and you will
империи И так дальше и вы это
support it And why the hell if it is
поддержите А нафига если она Нафига
needed then why did you include it in the
нужна то зачем вы включили её в
composition so here  and it's also not clear Well,
состав так вот и тоже непонятно Ну так
so don't ask me the question, but Why did they
вот задавайте не мне вопрос да Нафига
include it in your government? Why, instead of
включили в а своему власти Зачем вместо
doing everything right for Ufa, they're
того чтобы Уфе сделать всё нормально да
also taking the idea of ​​restoring the now
ещё берут типа восстанавливают теперь
destroyed Mariupol and everything else, and
разрушенный Мариуполь и всё остальное а
then you'll have to pay reparations and
потом ещё репарации будете платить и
you'll think about some of this It seems  I
будете думать каким-то этим Вроде я
heard that reparations are paid by a losing
слышал что репарации платят проигрышная
country Yes
страна Да
you Well probably Well look you've already
вы Ну наверно Ну смотри так уже ж
paid already your accounts have been frozen yes
платите уже арестованы ваши счета да за
abroad Yes all these are already being transferred to Ukraine
границей Да все эти уже передают Украине
for restoration this same re
на восстановление этоже ре найти их не
can't be found they found ml the rest all think
могут нашли мл остальные все считают
something can't find anything
что-то не могут никак найти
Oh really, here you are sitting, you don't
Ой реально вот вы сидите вы ничего не
know anything But you know that they
знаете Но вот это знаете что там что-то
can't find something there
не могут найти
Well, I'm not there together, so to speak, with
Да ну я же там не вместе так скажем с
Western accountants, what's up for now Well,
западными бухгалтерами что зайн пока Да
okay, let's see if someone breaks through to you there,
ну О'кей давайте к вам там кто-то
yeah  No, well, you, as Vladimir
прорывается да Нет ну вы как Владимир
Vladimirovich, can knock there and
Владимирович можете там стукнуть и
say busy for now And this is
сказать занят пока И это это шагу
probably breaking through to you, he says in
наверное к вам прорывается говорит у на
Ukraine, but you don’t listen to him.
Украине а вы его не слушайте вот
Take a listen, maybe he will tell you,
Возьмите послушайте может он вас скажет
you will start talking differently  you know it's
вы по-другому начте говорить знае
interesting
интересно года два
to meet like this for two years well here at least in
так встретиться ну тут же хотя бы в
chatroulette wait in two years there
чатрулет подожди через года два уже
will already be an independent Bashkartastan
будет Независимый башкартастан Ну
Okay why do you need such a look a rich
ладно Зачем вам смотри такое Богатое
state would be like that but as it is you give away all the oil
государство было бы так а так всю нефть
the area is almost like Bashkartastan
отдаёте площади почти как башкартастан
the population is half a million less Yes and
население На полмиллиона меньше Да а
lives in chocolate  from oil and you with oil
живёт в шоколаде от нефти а вы с нефтью
with gas and no well Qatar will be
с газом и нет ну Ката стане то ещё
more or less it seems to me everything is relatively
более-менее мне кажется всё относительно
good Well relative to Qatar Qatar no No well
хорошо Ну относительно Катара Катара не
well that's it Why look
Нет ну ну вот это да так Почему смотри
Qatar is so comparable with Bashkortostan
Катар так сравнимый с Башкортостана
lives awesomely spends there almost in
живёт офигенно проводит там чуть ли не
short  super everything you want and builds
короче супер всё что хочется и строит
so and
так а
Well okay in Ukraine as you say So we do
Ну ладно в Украине как скажите Так у нас
n't have oil gas if we had
нету нефти газа если бы у нас было
look we are comparing the same
смотри мы ж вот сравниваем одинаковые
Qatar and Bashkartastan in terms of territory
вот Катар и башкартастан по территории
it is almost the same so in terms of population
это почти тоже самое так по населению у
Qatar has 2 with what-  then
Катара 2 с чем-то миллиона у
Bashkortostan has three and something million, I saw
Башкортостана три с чем-то вот я видел
this comparison of how many barrels of oil
это сравнение барели нефти сколько
this one exports  Bashkartastan also had
экспортирует этот башкартастан тоже было
something comparable to a boat Yes, in my opinion,
что сравнимо с катером Да это по-моему
Bashkartastan has already
ещ башкартастан уже помоему давно уже
sold everything in Moscow a long time ago, so that's the point,
всё в Москве продал так вот Вот в том-то
sold and gave away Well, that's the
и дело продал а отдал Ну так вот в
point Yes, it turns out that Moscow is
том-то и дело Да что получается Москва
pumping out of you  all the money and he lives in
выкачивает из вас все деньги Так и живёт
luxury And
шикует А
you I even think I saw a
вы Я даже по-моему где-то видел
comparison somewhere that some four
сравнение что у каких-то четырёх
regions have a budget like I
областей бюджет как
think only spent on the improvement of
у по-моему только на благоустройство
Moscow, which is also yes yes and all you
Москвы тратил что тоже да да и всё вы
support a special military
поддерживаете специальную военную
operation would be like one  well I'm telling you
операцию бы одна как бы ну я же говорю
population
население
look at oil export look at Qatar
смотрите экспорт нефти смотрите Катар
Qatar exports half a million barrels of
Катар экспортирует полмиллиона баррелей
oil a day
нефти в день
E and this is Tatarstan that's not Bashkartastan I
Э а это Татарстан вот не башкартастан
apologize Tatarstan compared Yes Tatarstan
извиняюсь Татарстан сравнил Да Татарстан
exports half a million three times more
экспортирует пол милна в три раза больше
oil exports than Qatar Yes the
экспортирует нефти чем Катар Да
population of Qatar is 2.6 million Tatarstan 3  ,8
население Катара 2,6 млн Татарстана 3,8
million average salary in a boat 4 with a
млн зарплата средняя в катере 4 с по
piece of bucks in Tatarstan 620 bucks
штуки баксов в Татарстане 620 баксов у
you have comparable I  I think things are all about this, we
вас сравнимые я думаю вещи всё про это
can put a period on this for me, it's just the
можно на этом поставим точку мне просто
last moment, I'm just interested
последний момент мне просто интересно
when you watch some Russian bloggers on YouTube,
когда вот ну каких-то блогеров на Ютюбе
this is when they
смотришь российских это когда они в смыс
also go into chat roulette, I just
чат рулетку также заходят я просто
tried to understand that they may not
пытался понятно что они может быть не
post everything, well, where  conditionally they drown them,
всё выкладывают Ну где условно их топят
but they seem to have come across your
нуно они попадались вроде бы на ваших
kind of uh, too Well, serious bloggers
таких ээ тоже Ну серьёзных блогеров
who
которые
seem to have them, look at the
вроде бы их посмотришь на
Ukrainian ones when they post they
украинских когда они выкладывают они
spread fluff, brah, anyone, but for some reason
разносят пухо брах любого но почему-то
here, here, and which of the Ukrainian
здесь вот а а кого вы из украинских
bloggers do you know? No, I mean, No  but
блогеров знаете Нет ято в смысле Нет но
I mean I understand that they are bloggers
я име виду я понимаю что они блогеры
look I'll tell you so there are in short I
смотрите я вам скажу так есть короче я
see from the Ukrainian bloggers I
смотрю вот из украинских блогеров я
see there is one Andrey popk Yes you
смотрю есть такой Андрей попк Да вот
definitely have to look at him in short he
обязательно посмотрите он короче вот он
really takes apart all the Russians they are
реально всех русских разносит вот этих
afraid of all these bloggers I saw a couple of days ago
всех блогеров боятся вот пару дней назад
he
видел он этого Бабичева американского
also tore apart this American Babichev and yours about the
разнёс тоже так вот вашего про
Russian one, that is, the coolest one is
российского то есть вот самый крутой
this blogger Andrey Popk. If
этот блогер Андрей попк Вот его если
you watch him, he tore apart everyone based on the
будете смотреть вот он разносит всех по
facts. Yeah, that's what I watch. I don't know
фактам всех Ага вот я его смотрю Я
much.  what did I learn from him too, in
многого чего у него научился тоже вот в
logic, in thinking, subscribe
логике в мышлении подпишитесь
to him and watch
обязательно на него и посмотрите ээ
Russian bloggers, you will immediately understand that
русских блогеров сразу же поймёте что
they mean nothing, it's just strange that
они ничего не значит просто Странно что
our bloggers seem to be when I sit and watch I want to
наши блогеры вроде когда сижу смотрю
be just a little bit, so
Хочу Прямо именно быть немножко так
to speak, to move away from our
скажем отойти от именно от наших
bloggers, that  just on the neutral
блогеров что просто на нейтральной
side directly try to feel
стороне прямо попробовать прочувствовать
No damn it conveys so that it seems like well yes it
Нет блин доносит так что вроде ну да
seems like in fact so I say look
вроде по факту так я говорю вот смотри
here among here there is a Ukrainian blogger This is
вот среди вот есть украинский блогер Это
Andrey pop I was also in roulette at first I
Андрей поп Я сначала тоже в рулетке
just started watching it he so
Просто сил начал его смотреть он так
unpacks all these Russian bloggers by
расчехлять всех этих русских блогеров по
facts, just there all sorts of Uncle Slava
фактам вот просто там всяких дяди Славы
Babichev all all all all they in short
бабичево вся всех всех всех они короче
all either run away from him or start to
все или убегают от него или начинают
switch to some kind of shouting they can't
переходить на какие-то там крики они не
deduce from the facts so for example
могут по фактам вывести так вот например
I looked at Uncle Slava ask
тому Я смотрел н дяди слави спра скажи
if they say that there is Ukraine  attacked there
если говорят что там Украина напала там
on Donbass when it started there and everything Uncle
на Донбасс когда началась там и всё Дядя
Slava is floating merges because
Слава плывёт сливается потому что не
they can't in fact no Here I looked
могут они по факту нет Вот я смотрел
who Losev  Losev looked Losev Yes so
кого Лосев Лосев смотрел Лосев Да так
look this Andrey popok he is generally he
смотри этот Андрей попок он вообще он
called Losev to Battle Losev wrote
Лосева вызывал на Батл Лосев написал
recorded an appeal that no no I will not
записал обращение что нене я не буду с
fight with you because
тобой типа батлиться потому что Вот
Look really I am telling you I just
посмотри реально Я же говорю Я просто
have to run away Yes right now
уже должен убегать Да сечас
Yes fem rel I learned here  what I
Да фам рел я научился вот то что я с
was talking to you is actually how I
тобой говорил это вот фактически как у
took these methods from him that he
него взял вот эти методику которые он
says he is the coolest come on everything was
говорит он самый крутой давай всё было
not very well well this is an example of a fake in
не очень ну это ж пример фейко в
telegram
телеграме
come on Yes also everything is tied to the
давай Да тоже все щить обовязково на
blogger Andrey while I am not really surprised
блогера Андрея пока я е реально дивлюсь
really  cool dude what do you want from
вот реально крутый чувак якщо хочете от
so How do I talk yes I got used to
так Як я балакати да я в нього навчився
it I was amazed at it write right now on the
Я в нього дивився пишиться прям зараз на
channel Andr Bye Slava Ukraine write on y
канал Андр Пока Слава украини пись на й
Telegram right now axis VN
Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through scarg ORV in your ban  and very
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos are not shown to people sometimes do not
багато вдео не показуе людям вчасно не
show information about streams
показуе информация про стримы тому для
so that we Mali operational links
для того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
are written right now and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegrams okrim videos also interesting and
телеграми окрим вдео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we owe you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
constant operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that case show  you process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
write a
пиши а